Guide to the Women on the Job Records WAG.240
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files, 1968-2006.
  - Nassau County: Sexual Harassment Policy, 1994, 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Nassau County: The Wages of Inequality(CSEA/AFSCME Report), Mar 1983 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Nassau County: Wage Study, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Nassau County: Women Executives, 1981-1991 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Nassau Suffolk Contractor's Association, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Nassau Suffolk Council of Administrative Women in Education, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Nassau Suffolk Women's Bar Association, 1985, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - National Association of Women in Construction (NAWIC), undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - National Association of Women's Centers: Conference, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - National Committee on Pay Equity, 1985-1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - National Committee on Pay Equity: Job Evaluation: A Tool for Pay Equity, Nov 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - National Committee on Pay Equity: Pay Equity Activity in the Public Sector 1979-1989, Oct 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - National Committee on Pay Equity: Tenth Anniversary Conference and Celebration, Oct 20, 1989-Oct 22, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - National Council for Research on Women: Affirmative Action Quarterly, Volume I, Number 4, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Mother in the Workplace Study, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Court Reporters Foundation: Pay Equity, 1992, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - National Employment Lawyers Association, May 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - National Equal Pay Day, Apr 16, 2002, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - National Nurses Week, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1985-1992, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - National Organization for Women: Pay Equity Rally, Aug 25, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - National Puerto Rican Coalition (NPRC), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - New Directions: A Resource Center for Women, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union: Nassau County Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - New York State Assembly Task Force on Women's Issues: Comparable Worth: Every Women's Right, May 1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - New York State Association for Women in Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - New York State Association for Women in Administration: 2nd Annual Conference, Mar 5, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - New York State Coalition on Pay Equity (NYSPEC), 2000, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - New York State Court Reporters' Association, Feb 27, 2001, Nov 4, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights, 1984-1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights: Sexual Harassment, 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - New York State Legislative Advocacy: Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - New York State Pay Equity Coalition, Sep 2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - New York State Social Studies Review and Development Committee: Report, One Nation, Many Peoples, Jun 1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - New York State Women's Division, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - New York Women's Foundation, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Newman, Winn, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Newsletters: Other Organizations, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Nine to Five: National Association of Working Women, 1983-1984, 1988-1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Non-Traditional Employment for Women, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - North Hempstead, New York: Pay Equity Case Study, undated-1987, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program, 1987-1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program: Feasibility Study, 1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program: Meeting, Oct 1982 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program: Progress Report, Dec 1, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program: Proposal, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program: Proposal, Dec 1, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program: Report, May 3, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program: Report, May 10, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program: Report, May 14, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - New Support for Minority Women in Education, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Oceanside Public Schools: Workshop Distributed Material, Apr 20, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Oceanside School District: Sexual Harassment Policy, Oct 1993 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs (OFCCP), 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - One Hundred and Ten Center for Business and Professional Women, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Operating Budgets, 1981-1994 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Outreach and Registration Information, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Pay Equity, 1984-1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Pay Equity: Court Decisions, 1981-1986, 1991-1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Pay Equity: Examples Glen Cove and Central Islip, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Pay Equity: Project Material, 1987, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Pay Equity: Publicity, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Pay Equity: Maine, West Virginia, Florida, Connecticut, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Pay Equity: Minnesota, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Pay Equity, Strategies to Achieve, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity Testimony, Jan 22, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Plainview School District: Linda Donato Case, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Port Washington Water District, 1984-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Practical Guide to Women's Job Rights(WOJ), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Pregnancy Discrimination, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1982-1984, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Professional Women in Government (PWG), 1989, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Program to Advance Women's Employment in Non-Traditional Occupations(WOJ), undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Progress Report: Start-up Planning Grant Period, Jul 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Project Move Cartoon Book, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Project Notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Proposal: Long Island Women in the Economy, Dec 1, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Public Employees: CSEA, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Public School Employees, 1983-1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Public School Employees: Nassau County and NY State, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Publications and Reports: Lists, circa 1980, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 1984-1998, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Registration (WOJ), undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Reid and Priest, 1993-1994, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Reid and Priest: Sexual Harassment Training, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Religious Network for Equality for Women (RNEW), 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Religious Network for Equality for Pay Equality, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Resources for Program Development Inc., 1984, 1987, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Resources for Program Development, Inc.: Annual Meeting, Feb 12, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Resources for Program Development, Inc.: Board of Minutes, 1982-1987 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Resources for Program Development:, Inc.: Budgets, 1984-1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Resources for Program Development, Inc.: By-Laws, 1982, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Rivkin, Radler and Kremer, 1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Proposal, May 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Rockville Centre, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Rockville Centre: Pay Equity, 1983-1984, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Room Rentals: Universities, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Roslyn Elementary School: Sexual Harassment Policy, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Roslyn School District: Gender Equity, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Sachem Office Staff Association, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Sachem Office Staff Association: Legal Briefs, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Sachem School District Office Staff Rally, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Scholarship (On Board Boot Camp), 2006 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - School Applications (I), 1983, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - School Applications (II), 1983, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - School Applications, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Scrapbook, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Scrapbook, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Secretaries Day ("Raises Not Roses"), Apr 23, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Self-Help Action Center, Inc., 1987, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Sex Discrimination, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Sex Discrimination Survey, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Sexism, 1971-1988 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Sexual Assault: New York State Assembly, May 1986 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Sexual Discrimination at NYC Vocational Schools, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Sexual Discrimination Questionnaire, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Sexual Harassment Articles, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Sexual Harassment: Blue Collar Workers, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Sexual Harassment: Case Scenarios, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Sexual Harassment: Cases in New York, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Sexual Harassment: Chronology, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Sexual Harassment: Clippings, 1976-1993 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Sexual Harassment: College Surveys, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Sexual Harassment: Corporate Policy, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Sexual Harassment: Corporate Training, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Sexual Harassment: General (I), undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sexual Harassment: General (II), undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sexual Harassment: Government Pamphlets, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sexual Harassment: Governors Executive Order # 19, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sexual Harassment: Governor's Task Force on, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Sexual Harassment: Guide for Employees, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sexual Harassment: Guides and Definitions, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sexual Harassment: "Hostile Hallways" AAUW Survey, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sexual Harassment: League of Women Voters, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Sexual Harassment: Medical Institutions, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sexual Harassment: Meetings with Long Island Local Officials, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sexual Harassment: Meritor Savings Bank, FSB v. Vinson Supreme Court Decision, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Sexual Harassment: New York Firefighters, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Sexual Harassment: Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Sexual Harassment: Prevention (I), undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Sexual Harassment: Prevention (II), undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sexual Harassment: Prevention (III), undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Sexual Harassment: Prevention Workshop, Oct 22, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Sexual Harassment: Prevention Workshops, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Sexual Harassment: Prevention Workshops, 1993-1994, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Sexual Harassment: Prevention Workshops for Librarians, 1993, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Sexual Harassment: Project on the Status and Education of Women, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Sexual Harassment: Questionnaire, May 4, 1984, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Sexual Harassment: Resources Bibliography, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Sexual Harassment: Sample Policy Statement, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Sexual Harassment: School Clippings, 1986, 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Sexual Harassment: School Secrets, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Sexual Harassment: School Workshops, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Sexual Harassment: Student Guide, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Sexual Harassment: Studies by Donald Maypole, Sep 1982, Nov 1983 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Sexual Harassment: Teachers Guide, Massachusetts Dept of Education, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Sexual Harassment: Teachers Handbook: Minnesota Department of Education, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Sexual Harassment: Title IX, 1975-1982, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Sexual Harassment: Transparencies, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Sexual Harassment: Universities, Jun 1905-1990 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Sexual Harassment: Videos, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Sexual Harassment: Workshops, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Sexual Harassment in Employment by Debra L. Raskin, Jun 1989 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Sexual Harassment Second Annual Conference, Mar 5, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Sexual Harassment Training, 1991-1993, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Sexual Harassment Training: Law Firms, 1994, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Sexual Harassment Training: Libraries, 1991-1993, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Sexual Harassment Training: Meyer, Suozzi and Klein, Jan 1996 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Sexual Harassment Training: Weiss Instruments, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Shareholder Education Guide(WOJ), 2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sinnott, George: Pay Equity Resources, 1985, 1993, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Smithtown School Employees Association, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Speech Materials, 1982-1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Speech Materials (K. Jeffers), 1989, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Sperry Corporation: Correspondence with Lillian McCormick, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Sponsors, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1989-1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Strategies to Advance Women in Public School Administration(WOJ), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Suffolk Community College: Sexual Harassment Training, May 26, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Suffolk Community College: Sexual Harassment Workshop, May 26, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Suffolk County: Affirmative Action Administration, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Suffolk County: Ask Information and Referral System, undated, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Suffolk County: Comparable Worth, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Suffolk County: Displaced Homemakers, 1981-1982, 1990-1991, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Suffolk County: Pay Equity, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Suffolk County: Pay Equity, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Suffolk County: Pay Equity Legislation, 1985-1990, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Suffolk County: Pay Equity Study, Oct 1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Suffolk County: Police Proposal, 1983-1984, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Suffolk County: Sexual Harassment Policy, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Suffolk County: Sexual Harassment Public Law #9, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Suffolk County: Re-classification, circa 1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Suffolk County: Wage Discrimination (clippings), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Suffolk County: Women's Equal Rights Congress Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Suffolk County: Women in Government Exempt Employees, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Suffolk County and Nassau County School Districts: Salary Data, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Suffolk County Association of Nurses (SCAN), 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Suffolk County Civil Service: Affirmative Action, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Suffolk County Civil Service: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Suffolk County Civil Service: Employment Data, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Suffolk County Civil Service: Ethnicity, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Suffolk County Civil Service: Job Descriptions, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Suffolk County Civil Service: Rules, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Suffolk County Human Rights Commission, 1983, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Suffolk County Nurses Association (Task Force Member), 1982-1986 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Suffolk County Office for Women, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Suffolk County Police Academy: Sexual Harassment, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Suffolk County Police Department: Hiring Program, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Suffolk County School District: Assessed Valuation, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Suffolk County School District: Salary Data, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Suffolk County School District: Personal Data, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Summary of Data on Directory Requests, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - SUNY Westbury: Sexual Harassment, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Surveys and Studies, 1983-1987 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Survey and Studies: Hay Group, undated, Jun 1989 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Survey of Sexual Harassment Prevention Policies at Long Island Colleges and Universities(WOJ), undated, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Task Force, undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Task Force, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Task Force, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Task Force, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Task Force, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Task Force, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Task Force, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Task Force, Jan 1988-May 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Task Force, Jun 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Task Force, Jan 1989-Mar 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Task Force, May 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Task Force, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Task Force, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Task Force, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Task Force, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Task Force, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Task Force, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Task Force, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Task Force, 2000-2004 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Task Force: Attendance Lists, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Task Force: Correspondence, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Task Force: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Task Force: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Task Force Goals, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Task Force: History and Policy Statement, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Task Force: Mission Statement, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Task Force: Member List, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Task Force: News Briefs, 1986-1992, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Task Force Survey, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - TECH-Prep Program, 1993-1994, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Telephone Bills: New York, 1981-1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Telephone Questionnaire: Local Government Women Executives, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Three Village School District Pay Equity Profile, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: Women's Educational Equity Act Program, 1978, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Labor: A Working Woman's Guide to Her Job Rights, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of Labor: "Equal Pay for Equal Work", undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - United States Department of Labor: Glass Ceiling Initiative, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - United States Department of Labor: Transparencies, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau, 1979-1988, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau, Pay Equity, 1998-2000, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - United Way of Long Island, 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Victims Information Bureau of Suffolk, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Volunteers, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Wage Gap Studies, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Wantagh Education Secretaries Association: Pay Equity, 1988, 1992, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Website, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Westchester County: Sexual Harassment Policy, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women (W.O.W.), 1981-1988, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Where are the Women?: Event, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Where are the Women?: Project, 1998-2002 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Women Administrators in Government: Affirmative Action Press Release and Report, 1984-1985, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Women Artists on Long Island, 1986, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Women Economic Developers of Long Island (WEDLI), 1984-1985, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Women in Blue Collar Trades, 1982, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Women in County Government: Employment Report(WOJ), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Women in Education Administration, 1968-1987, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Women in Employment: Questionnaire, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Women in the Workplace(newsletter), 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Women in the Trades: Graphics, Signs, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Women in the Trades: Resources, Events, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Womanspace in Great Neck, 1987-1994 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Women's Action Alliance, Inc., undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Women's Alliance for Job Equity (WAJE), 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Women's Center of Huntington, The, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Women's Equal Rights Congress Committee (WERC), 1982-1983, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Women's Faculty Association, 1970-1988 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Women's History Week, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Women's Labor Day Pay Equity Rally, Sep 22, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Women's Labor Day Rally, Sep 22, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - "Women's Place in Technology": Grant Proposal, May 14, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Women's Technical Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Women's Way Correspondence, Mar 25, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Women's Workspace Audit, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Working Conditions Cases, 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Working for Pay Equity: Blueprint for Local Community Action, undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Working Smarts Program (I), undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Working Smarts Program (II), undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Working Smarts Program, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Working Smarts Program: Evaluations, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Working Smarts Program: Nassau Co. Association of Women Police, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Working Smarts Program: Outreach, 1983-1992 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Working Smarts Program: Speaking Engagements, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Working Smarts Program: Speeches, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Working Smarts Program: Volunteer Educators, undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Working Smarts Project for Teenagers, 1984-1992, undated (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Working Smarts Project for Teenagers, undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Working Smarts Project for Teenagers: Workshop Materials for Volunteers, Oct 17, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Working Women Count, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Working Women's Institute, undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Workplace Reports(WOJ), 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA): Pay Equity Proposal, 1987-1988, undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA): Pay Equity Workshop, 1989-1990, undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Buttons, Bumper Sticker, Videos, and Photographs, circa 1980-1999 (Box 12)